Hey guys and welcome to day six of the attraction blueprint,
Hola chicos, bienvenidos al sexto día de nuestro plan de seducción.
so you've done all the hard work right, we've got the confidence, got the mindset,
Ya hicieron todo el trabajo duro, ¿verdad? Tenemos confianza, la actitud correcta,
we know how to talk to a girl, we've built an amazing connection through conversation,
sabemos cómo acercarnos a una mujer, hemos construido una gran conexión a través de la conversación
she's feeling the energy still in the vibe, um
, y ella todavía siente esa energía positiva.
, by the way, I love how women use that word,
Por cierto, me encanta cómo las mujeres
um, vibe check, uh, that's like their catchphrase right now,
usan la expresión "dick check"; está muy de moda ahora mismo. ¿
why she get good vibes from him, well, it's your job as the man to give her those vibes,
Por qué se siente tan bien con él? Bueno, es tu trabajo, como hombre, transmitirle esa energía positiva.
um, that's why the energy transfer so...
Por eso es tan
important so today we're going to talk about the clothes and what i'm going to do
importante el intercambio de energía. Hoy vamos a cerrar el trato y compartiré
is i'm going to give you few of my favorite closing techniques um because what
algunas de mis técnicas favoritas con ustedes. Porque lo que
happens is and this is so funny um i actually did a bunch of street interviews with
suele pasar, y esto es un poco gracioso, es que
women a while back and it's one of the like biggest complaints about women is
hace un tiempo entrevisté a muchas mujeres en la calle, y una de las quejas más comunes fue: "
he didn't ask me out like we just kept talking and i put him in the friend zone
No me invitó a salir". Seguimos hablando, y lo dejé en la friendzone
because he wouldn't lead and on especially on dating apps um women want to as soon
porque no dio el primer paso. En las apps de citas, las mujeres quieren tomar la iniciativa
as they feel a connection to lead and close and i literally heard one girl say it's
y dar el primer paso en cuanto sienten una conexión. Una vez escuché a una chica decir: "¡Esta es
called a dating app,
una app de citas,
it's not a friendship app, ask me out,
no de amistad! ¡Invítame a salir!". ¡
It's so funny when i heard her say that like ah man
Fue muy gracioso! ¡
that's so true and it's a big mistake lot of guys make,
Y es verdad! Muchos chicos cometen el error
you're scared to close because you're scared of rejection,
de dar el primer paso por miedo al rechazo.
but we are talked about active reframing and how
Pero ya hemos
to get around that so i'm not really worried about that,
hablado de cómo cambiar de actitud activamente y superar este miedo, así que no me preocupa.
but let's talk about how to increase your success rate with closing,
Hablemos de cómo aumentar tus posibilidades de dar el primer paso.
first thing i want to talk about is on the dating apps
Primero, quiero hablar de las apps de citas
themselves - because I think this is where most of you guys are at,
en sí, ya que creo que la mayoría las usa
your dating apps, let's talk about how we close uh,
. Hablemos de cómo dar el primer paso.
so when it comes to closing a dating app, your job through conversation,
En una app de citas, lo importante es la conversación.
and look, you're using that fev protocol with humor,
Usa el método FEV, el humor
with storytelling, using all those things to build
y crea
emotional investment through text messaging a dating app,
una conexión emocional por mensaje de texto
and by the way, secret weapon, if you have the ability use a voice note,
.
voice notes are absolutely killer on dating apps,
¡Los mensajes de voz son increíblemente efectivos! En las apps de citas
um, but as having that conversation with her a dating app,
... bueno, cuando chateas con ella,
your job is to bring her in emotionally,
y crea
to build her emotional investment into going out with you,
una conexión emocional
you get her to the point where she has to meet you, she has to see you in person,
, inicias un encuentro y haces que quiera conocerte en persona.
and you use all the advanced communication, the frameworks to get her to that point,
Todas las técnicas de comunicación avanzadas que puedas imaginar.
so what you're looking for is you're looking for signs of investment,
Buscas
this can be long replies, um, this can be her asking you amazing questions,
señales de interés: respuestas largas, preguntas pertinentes
um, lot of emojis, uh, really, it's basically reciprocated effort,
, muchos emojis... Es básicamente un toma y daca:
is she giving you as much effort in the conversation as you're giving her,
¿se está esforzando tanto como tú?
and once you notice that investment's high and
Una vez
once you notice she's into the conversation,
que sabes que está interesada,
the rule that kind of use here guys, um, and it's it's cliche, but it absolutely is true,
la regla es (es un cliché, pero es cierto):
is strike while they aren't hot, lot of guys, i see this time and time again,
aprovecha la oportunidad mientras aún esté cautivada. Veo a muchos hombres
lot of guys make the mistake of waiting until the conversation dies down,
cometer constantemente el error de esperar a que la conversación se calme.
oh crap, i don't have anything else to say, let me ask her out,
¡Uf! ¿Tienes algo más que decir? Déjame preguntarle si quiere salir contigo.
no, you get her to an emotional crescendo and then you capitalize on that emotion,
No, la pones emocionalmente nerviosa y luego explotas esa emoción. ¿
how you that emotion to date?
Cómo consigues una cita así?
oh my god, this is so amazing, we've got to see if this is real in person,
¡Guau, eso es increíble! Tenemos que comprobar si es real cuando nos conozcamos en persona.
like this has been an amazing conversation,
Esta conversación fue fantástica;
i can't wait to see how good this is actually going to be with the real you,
ya estoy emocionado por ver lo bien que es contigo en persona.
so you're getting her to that emotional peak,
La llevas a un punto álgido emocional;
she's into you, she's getting the vibes as she says,
está totalmente involucrada, lo siente, como ella misma dice...
um, and then you're taking advantage of that emotional high,
y luego aprovechas esa euforia;
that's when you move into the close, and here is my absolute favorite close,
ahora es el momento de cerrar. Y esta es mi técnica de cierre favorita:
um, it works a ton and i haven't had lot
funciona de verdad, y rara vez he
of negative feedback when guys have use this close,
recibido comentarios negativos cuando los hombres la usan
because it gets a micro commitment, it's true and it just works,
porque crea una especie de minicompromiso. Es cierto, y funciona.
so get to that emotional high point, first thing you say is,
Para alcanzar ese clímax emocional, empieza diciendo: "
i don't about you, but i absolutely hate these dating apps,
No sé tú, pero odio las apps de citas".
um, whatever your opinion of them is chances are she's going to say something
Independientemente de tu opinión, probablemente responderá con un
of micro compliance of oh my god me too or you have no idea or she'll give you
"¡Dios mío, yo también!" o "¡No tienes ni idea!", o
something that agrees with your statement so you have no idea how much hate these
dirá algo que confirme tu afirmación, como: "¡No tienes ni idea de cuánto odio
dating apps i much prefer the real world or some variation of or something about
las apps de citas; prefiero el mundo real!" o algo similar. Una variación podría ser: "
like hate the online world i like the real world better um but when she says
Odio el mundo online; prefiero el mundo real". Pero si dice
something that agrees with that statement what she's done is she's ' given you micro
algo que confirma esta afirmación, te está ofreciendo un
compliance of the real world,
vistazo a la realidad.
so you give her that, I don't about you, but I hate dating apps,
Así que responde: "No sé tú, pero odio las apps de citas;
I much prefer the real world, yes, me too, great, why don't we,
prefiero el mundo real". "Sí, yo también". "Genial, ¿por qué no?".
and then you suggest the date, never ever ever ask these two questions in person,
Y luego propón una cita. Nunca hagas estas dos preguntas en persona,
a dating app, in a relationship, in marriage,
en una app de citas, en una relación, en el matrimonio;
never, never, as long as you're dating women,
nunca, de verdad, nunca, cuando salgas con alguien.
ask these two questions, when you're free, what do you want to do,
Nunca hagas estas dos preguntas cuando estés soltero: "¿Qué te gustaría hacer
that is kryptonite in the dating world, why?
?". Esta es la clave del éxito en el mundo de las citas. ¿Por qué?
shows zero effort, zero leadership,
Demuestra una completa falta de compromiso, liderazgo y
zero confidence, i say suggest the date,
confianza. Yo digo: Sugiere una cita,
and what i mean by that is, why don't we go do this at this?
y con eso quiero decir: "¿Por qué no hacemos algo ahora mismo?".
on this date, or i bet we would have so much fun doing this,
Ese mismo día —o: Apuesto a que lo pasaríamos genial haciendo eso,
this time of this date, oh my god, you're going to have so much fun when we go do this,
ahora mismo, ese mismo día— ¡Dios mío, te lo pasarías genial si lo hiciéramos,
this time or this date, you're telling her what you want to go do, when and where,
ahora mismo o ese mismo día!— Dile qué te gustaría hacer, cuándo y dónde.
when you do that, you're going to get three possible answers from that suggestion,
Entonces tendrás tres posibles respuestas.
first possible answer, best case scenario is sounds great,
La primera, en el mejor de los casos, es: "¡Genial,
let's do it, second possible answer you're going to get from that is:
hagámoslo!". La segunda posible respuesta es: "
probably scheduling conflict right, you just gave her very specific time in a date,
Seguro que ya tiene planes". Acabas de darle una fecha muy concreta.
we live in a very busy world, she may have something going on, and by the way,
Vivimos en un mundo ajetreado; puede que ya tenga algo planeado. Y por cierto:
to increase your odd success, always set the first date Monday through Thursday,
para aumentar tus posibilidades de éxito, programa siempre tu primera cita de lunes a jueves.
women are typically bit busier, already have plans, Friday, Saturday, Sunday,
Las mujeres suelen estar un poco más ocupadas; ya tienen planes para el viernes, sábado y domingo.
so just to increase your odds of her being free,
Así que, para aumentar las posibilidades de que esté libre,
Monday through Thursday is typically better first date um time slot,
el mejor momento para una primera cita suele ser de lunes a jueves.
so those are the first two answers you're
Estas son las dos primeras respuestas que obtendrás
going to get from um that close if you do it right,
si juegas bien tus cartas.
third uh,
La tercera, eh...
it's really funny, the third thing women will do when you suggest date
esta es un poco graciosa... Cuando invitas a salir a una mujer,
is they will literally ignore that you just said that and keep talking to you,
a menudo ignoran por completo lo que acabas de decir y siguen hablando.
it's it's like they don't know what, it's like
Es como si no entendieran, como si
they think we don't know what just happened,
pensaran que no sabes qué pasó.
but it actually frustrates lot of guys,
Esto frustra a muchos hombres,
but you've got confidence, you know how to reframe this,
pero tienes confianza y sabes cómo darle la vuelta a la situación.
and the reframe there is just not yet, she's not ready to go a date with me yet,
La solución es que ella aún no está lista para una cita.
so i'm going to go back to building in emotional investment,
Así que empezaré a involucrarme emocionalmente de nuevo,
i'm going to go back to the fev protocol
usaré el método FEV
and i'm going to wait until i get another emotional investment crescendo,
y esperaré una nueva conexión emocional,
another emotional investment buy in, and then i'm going to try again,
un nuevo compromiso, antes de volver a intentarlo.
and when i try again, i'm probably one of those three answers again,
Y cuando lo vuelva a intentar, probablemente volveré a dar una de esas tres respuestas.
if it happens a second time, feel free to call it out,
Si vuelve a ocurrir, no dudes en decírselo con
something as simple as you know what you just did, or i know you saw that, or hey
algo sencillo como "Sabes lo que acabas de hacer", "Sé que lo viste" o incluso "
we ain't here to play games,
No estamos aquí para jugar".
call her out on ignoring that message she obviously read and just have fun with it.
Deja claro que ignora el mensaje, que claramente ha leído, y tómatelo con humor.
um, this is part of that flirty interaction, some women do play hard to get,
Todo forma parte del juego de la seducción. Algunas mujeres se hacen las difíciles,
some women do like for some reason make you really earn a date with them,
mientras que otras, por una razón u otra, te conseguirán una cita,
especially if they're getting lot of attention,
sobre todo si reciben mucha atención.
which if you're going after an attractive woman,
Si estás buscando a una mujer atractiva (
hey to break it to you, she's getting lot of attention,
y créeme, recibe mucha atención),
um, so you might have to go through this like emotional investment,
puede que tengas que involucrarte emocionalmente:
ask out, emotional investment, ask out, emotional investment, call her out.
invítala a salir, muéstrale cariño, invítala de nuevo a salir, muéstrale cariño y luego tócala un poco.
um, so you might have to go through that iteration a couple times, but i promise you,
Puede que tengas que repetir este paso un par de veces, pero te prometo que
that framework absolutely works if you did the job of the conversation,
este método funciona a la perfección si has preparado bien la conversación y
building the emotional investment on the front in,
has establecido una conexión emocional desde el principio.
and guys, like when you're doing this in person, almost a same happens,
Y chicos, si lo hacen en persona, funciona básicamente igual.
the only thing tell guys to do in person
Te recomiendo que
is before you start the conversation with her, give
antes de la conversación.
her a like pre-framed time exit of hey,
hagas una breve introducción
you was just on my way to the gym, i got a couple minutes, i just want to tell you,
"Ibas de camino al gimnasio, tengo dos minutos, solo quería decirte...".
give her the compliment or give her your opening line or just like pre-frame that of hey,
Hazle un cumplido o usa tu frase inicial, o prepárate
i was just on the way to a meeting, but had to come say hello to you,
para decir: "Oye, iba de camino a una reunión, pero tuve que pasar...
um, i've only got a couple minutes - going to meet somebody,
eh, solo tengo dos minutos, tengo que encontrarme con alguien".
but brief frame that like time constraint,
Sin duda, enfatiza este límite de tiempo,
because what that does for her is it takes the
porque
pressure off for her of thinking that you're going to be there.
la hace sentir segura y evita que piense que estarás ahí para siempre.
her for an hour um that is actually fear a lot of girls have is oh my god i don't want
Muchas chicas tienen miedo de pasar una hora con ella: "¡Dios mío, no quiero
to talk i'm going somewhere i don't want to be late um so if you pre-frame this exit
hablar, tengo que irme, no quiero llegar tarde!". Así que planificar la reunión
um it really helps her just like kind of um take her guard down to know that you're not
la ayuda mucho; la tranquiliza porque sabe que no solo
going to sit and talk to her for 30 minutes um also watch your body language like kind
charlarás con ella durante 30 minutos. Presta atención también a tu lenguaje corporal:
of keep an open body language sir so you're not like threatening um keep your distance
mantén una postura abierta para no parecer amenazante. Mantén cierta distancia,
a little bit keep an open body language and as you're in the conversation you can square
pero sigue siendo amable. A medida que la conversación avance, podrás
up with her um as she opens and welcomes to that in that in-person interaction
adaptarte a ella, ya que se mostrará más abierta y disponible durante la interacción cara a cara.
um and then as you're going to the close there you're going to once again transition
Y cuando llegue el momento de terminar la conversación, gestiona la transición.
um and what i like to do is i like to bring up the like high point of the conversation
Me gusta aprovechar el momento. Un momento clave de conversación.
so if she like got really excited talking about let's just say her trip to japan as i'm
Por ejemplo, si habla con entusiasmo de su viaje a Japón,
going to close um i would like japan i really want to know more about that let's connect
puedo terminar diciendo: "Me encantaría aprender más sobre Japón. ¿Quizás podríamos volver a vernos
and go grab a drink or it talks about
y tomar algo?".
Maybe her favorite type of food,
Podría estar elogiando su comida favorita: "
oh my god, I can't wait to take you to this place to go get that, let's connect and go,
¡Dios mío, qué ganas de llevarte a un sitio donde puedas comer eso! ¡Sigamos en contacto y vamos!", y contándome
and couple of things you can do there, I like getting a phone number closed,
todo lo que tiene que hacer. Me encantaría tener su número de teléfono,
um, but lot of guys uh still intimidated to do that, so easiest way to do it is um,
pero muchos hombres todavía no se atreven a pedírselo. La forma más fácil es
you literally can go through the communication
repasar las técnicas de comunicación habituales y la etiqueta
techniques and protocols and hey let's connect on instagram,
y sugerir: "¡Oye, conectémonos en Instagram!".
very non-invasive, very non-threatening, hey, why don't we?
Totalmente discreto, sin ser amenazante. ¿Por qué no?
man of intention, be intentional, lead the conversation, lead to the close,
Así que ten confianza, toma la iniciativa, lidera la conversación, termina
and then get out of there and then leave her a high note,
y despídete
crack a joke about something you just said,
. Haz una broma sobre lo que se dijo,
like i still can't believe you said japan was your favorite vacation ever,
como: "¡Todavía no puedo creer que dijeras que Japón fueron tus mejores vacaciones!"
um, as you're like walking out there,
al irte,
or it still trips me out that really your favorite food group is a salad,
o: "Todavía me sorprende que la ensalada sea tu comida favorita;
i just don't understand that, and then walk away, leave her on some type of joke,
no lo entiendo". Despídete y
some type of high note as you're exiting that conversation,
termina la conversación con una nota positiva, quizás con una broma,
just so her last memory of you is...
para que
a good emotion guys, so hope that helps you,
te recuerde con cariño. Espero que esto te ayude.
man, there's so much more to the actual game of closing that we can get into,
Hay mucho más que decir sobre el arte de cerrar una conversación,
um, but this is you know little over 10 minute video that i just want to give
pero este video de 10 minutos te mostrará
you to really give you the techniques to close on so um social media or dating app,
técnicas para cerrar en redes sociales o apps de citas,
but also some techniques to employ in person,
así como en conversaciones cara a cara.
so guys that's it for how to close, i know it was a short video,
Hasta aquí las técnicas de cierre. Sé que fue un video corto,
but i promise you these techniques do work if you try them um so...
pero te prometo que estas técnicas funcionan si las pruebas.
tomorrow I'm actually going to go into a little bonus with you of something you
¡Nos vemos mañana! Tengo un pequeño extra para ti, algo
absolutely need to know and I cannot wait to go with you um because it's
importante. Me emociona mucho compartirlo contigo porque
something I've done a ton of research on and have kind of nailed down a couple
he investigado mucho e identificado algunos
specifics um so yeah guys can't wait to see it or not I yes I know I'm leaving
puntos clave. ¿Tienes curiosidad? Lo sé,
it open for a reason just because it's a fun topic to go over uh a little bonus
lo estoy manteniendo deliberadamente en secreto porque es un tema fascinante. Es un pequeño extra
that I put together for you um but that's it guys I'll see you tomorrow's video
que he preparado especialmente para ti. ¡Eso es todo por mañana!
do me a favor go approach women and clothes now that you've worked through everything else.
Ahora que lo has asimilado todo, acércate a las mujeres y cierra el trato.
go close, let us know how those closes went, let us know how many closes were successful,
Cuéntanos cómo te fue, cuántas veces lo lograste y
let us know where you stumbled so we can give you some feedback, but go close today,
dónde fallaste, para que podamos darte algunos consejos. Pero hoy: cierra el trato y
go find someone to make a connection with today, bye guys.
crea conexiones. ¡Hola!